export const quizQuestion = [
  {
    question: "Prime Minister of Pakistan nation's heart:",
    option1: "Imran Khan",
    option2: "Nawaz Sharif",
    option3: "Bilawal Bhutto",
    option4: "Maryam Nawaz",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Prime Minister of India?",
    option1: "Rahul Gandhi",
    option2: "Butcher of Gujrat (Modi)",
    option3: "Rakesh Shukla",
    option4: "Navjod Singh Sidhu",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is national game of Pakistan?",
    option1: "Cricket",
    option2: "Hockey",
    option3: "Badminton",
    option4: "Football",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Capital of Pakistan is?",
    option1: "Karachi",
    option2: "Lahore",
    option3: "Islamabad",
    option4: "Quetta",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was captiain in 1992 world cup for Pakistan?",
    option1: "Saeed Anwar",
    option2: "Wasim Akram",
    option3: "Saqlain Mushtaq",
    option4: "Imran Khan",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Currency of America is:",
    option1: "Dollar",
    option2: "Pound",
    option3: "Euro",
    option4: "None of above",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "National animal of  is:",
    option1: "Wolf",
    option2: "Lion",
    option3: "Tiger",
    option4: "Markhor",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "National language of Pakistan is:",
    option1: "Punjabi",
    option2: "Pashto",
    option3: "Urdu",
    option4: "Sindhi",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Nation flower of Pakistan is:",
    option1: "Rose",
    option2: "Jasmine",
    option3: "Sun Flower",
    option4: "None of above",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "High populated province of Pakistan is:",
    option1: "Punjab",
    option2: "Sindh",
    option3: "KPK",
    option4: "Balochistan",
    answer: 1,
  },
];
